let quizz = [
    {
    question: " If A : B = 7 : 9 and B : C = 3 : 5, then A : B : C is equal to ?",
    option: [
        "7 : 9 : 5",
        " 7 : 9 : 15",
        "21: 35: 45",
        "21: 35: 45",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "If 1=3 2=3 3=5 4=4 5=4 Then, 6=??",
    option: [
        "5",
        "6",
        "3",
        "4",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Add 8.563 and 4.8292.",
    option: [
        "13.3932",
        "13.3922",
        "14.3942",
        "13.3942",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Which is greater than 4?",
    option: [
        "-4",
        "5",
        "3",
        "-5",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "Simplify: (4 – 5) – (13 – 18 + 2).",
    option: [
        "2",
        "3",
        "1",
        "-1",
    ],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: "What is |-26|?",
    option: [
        "26",
        "-26",
        "0",
        "1",
    ],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: "Multiply: (x – 4)(x + 5).",
    option: [
        "x2 + 5x - 20,",
        "x2 - 4x - 20",
        "x2 - x - 20",
        "x2 + x - 20",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: " Find the value of 3 + 2 • (8 – 3) .",
    option: [
        "15",
        "11",
        "23",
        "13",
    ],
    answer: 4,
},
{
    question: "The ratio of the length of a school ground to its width is 5 : 2. If the width is 40m, then the length is ,",
    option: [
        "200m",
        "100m",
        "300m",
        "180m",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "What is 5% of 50% of 500 ?",
    option: [
        "12.5",
        "13.4",
        "17.2",
        "18.3",
    ],
    answer: 1,
},
{
    question: "What is 32% of 3/8th of 5000 ?",
    option: [
        "700",
        "600",
        "780",
        "820",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "4, 12, 36, ?, 324, 972,..",
    option: [
        "103",
        "108",
        "112",
        "118",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "12, 15, 21, 30, 42, 57, ?",
    option: [
        "72",
        "73",
        "75",
        "74",
    ],
    answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "Find the missing number in the following series. 4, 18, ..., 100, 180, 294",
    option: [
        "59",
        "48",
        "41",
        "57",
    ],
    answer: 2,
},
{
    question: "A and B together can do a piece of work in 12 days, while B alone can do finish it in 30 days. A alone can finish the work in",
    option: [
        "29",
        "28",
        "20",
        "27",
    ],
    answer: 3,
}

]